<TngnWsvc>

    <Class name="asmx">

        <!-- ======================================================================= -->

        <RunScript> <!-- <include file='AppData/XmlDoc/Asmx.xml' path='TngnWsvc/Class[@name="asmx"]/RunScript/*'/> -->
            <note title="Development logging">
                This method contains a number of log commands that may be used during development, but should be commented out in production code.<br/>
                <br/>
                These commands are not part of the public API, since the logging infrastructure hasn't been initialized at this point, and they are all a little bit different and write to different locations.<br/>
                <br/>
                I want these commands to be available for developers to use as needed, but at the same time I want to minimize the amount of clutter they create. Hence, I've attempted to keep them on a single line, including an in-line comment.<br/>
            </note>
            <br/>
            <note title="Runtime settings">
                The runtime settings are built using values in Web.config, but since Outpost31 doesn't reference the TingenWebService project, the values are converted into a dictionary instead of a strongly-typed object. This makes it easier to pass to Outpost31.Core.TngnWsvcSession.Start(), at the expense of making the class a little uglier.<br/>
                <br/>
                Care must be taken to ensure the keys in Web.config match the keys expected by the code.<br/>
            </note>
            <br/>
            <note type="caution" title="Important!">
                Do not change the names of the following parameters:
                <list type="bullet">
                    <item>origOptObj</item>
                    <item>origScriptParam</item>
                </list>
                For some reason, changing these names causes the web service to fail.
            </note>
        </RunScript>

        <!-- ======================================================================= -->

    </Class>

</TngnWsvc>